https://karigirl.com/privacy1.html

Lhandslide Studios
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use
personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy
before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site,
you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These
practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only
apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis.
You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to
make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be
used.
Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy
are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted
at those sites.
Collection of Information
We collect no personal information from you at anytime during the browsing or purchasing process. If you register for the forum a user ID will be saved on our database so you can log on and download files. At no time is your email used for any marketing purposes or newsletter activities.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
This site does not use cookies to track any of your movements through our site.
Distribution of Information
We do not distribute any of your information to third parties at anytime.
Commitment to Data Security
Your personally identifiable
information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors
(who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to
this information.
Privacy Contact Information
If you have any questions,
concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the
information below:
E-mail: support (at) karigirl.com
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this
policy will be posted.
